{
    "subject": "resource/Katherine_Vaz",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Katherine Vaz (born August 26, 1955) is an American writer. A Briggs-Copeland Fellow in Fiction at Harvard University (2003-9), a 2006-7 Fellow of the Radcliffe Institute for Advanced Study, and the Fall, 2012 Harman Fellow at Baruch College in New York, she is the author of the critically acclaimed novel Saudade (St. Martin\u2019s Press, 1994), the first contemporary novel about Portuguese-Americans from a major New York publisher. It was optioned by Marlee Matlin/Solo One Productions and selected in the Barnes & Nobles Discover Great New Writers series.Her second novel, Mariana, (HarperCollins, 1997), was selected by the Library of Congress as one of the Top 30 International Books of 1998 and has been translated into six languages.Vaz's  first short story collection Fado & Other Stories received the 1997 Drue Heinz Literature Prize  and her second collection, Our Lady of the Artichokes, won the 2007 Prairie Schooner Book Prize.Vaz is a recipient of a Literature Fellowship from the National Endowment for the Arts (1993)  and the Davis Humanities Institute Fellowship (1999). She has been named by the Luso-Americano as one of the Top 50 Luso-Americanos of the twentieth century  and is the first Portuguese-American to have her work recorded for the Library of Congress, housed in the Hispanic Division. The Portuguese-American Women\u2019s Association (PAWA) named her 2003 Woman of the Year.  She was appointed to the six-person U.S. Presidential Delegation to open the American Pavilion at the World\u2019s Fair/Expo 98 in Lisbon. She lives in New York City and the Springs area of East Hampton with Christopher Cerf, whom she married in July, 2015.",
    "human_readable": "Katherine Vaz is a renowned American writer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9640604257583618,
            "question": "Is Katherine Vaz a writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8154963254928589,
            "question": "What is Katherine Vaz known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5985779762268066,
            "question": "Are there any specific themes or genres that Katherine Vaz often writes about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5853663086891174,
            "question": "What nationality is Katherine Vaz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5487977266311646,
            "question": "Where is Katherine Vaz from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5254406929016113,
            "question": "What kind of works does Katherine Vaz write?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45625731348991394,
            "question": "Has Katherine Vaz won any awards for her writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45317572355270386,
            "question": "What are some of Katherine Vaz's most popular works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3602462410926819,
            "question": "Has Katherine Vaz published any books recently?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34360405802726746,
            "question": "Where can readers find more information about Katherine Vaz and her work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Katherine Vaz is a renowned American writer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1691_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Katherine Vaz published any books recently?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1691_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Katherine Vaz's most popular works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1691_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Katherine Vaz won any awards for her writing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1691_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1691_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1691_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1691_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1691_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1691_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1691_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1691_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1691_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1691_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1691_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Katherine Vaz is a renowned American writer\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents mention Katherine Vaz as an author, specifically stating that she is the author of various novels and collections. The documents also mention her awards and fellowships, which further supports the fact that she is a renowned writer in the American literary scene."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Katherine Vaz is a renowned American writer.\" They mention her fellowships, novels, and collections, which are indicative of her being a well-regarded author. Additionally, they highlight the international recognition of her work through awards and translations, further supporting the claim of her renown."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}